Gabriele Miano

Software Engineer

https://www.gabrielemiano.it/

Milan, Italy

info@gabrielemiano.it miano.gabriele@gmail.com

Summary

Passionate web developer with 10 years of experience in designing, developing, testing web applications.

Proven ability to refactoring applications.

Strong interesting for the new technologies.

Skills

Javascript / Typescript / Angular 2 / Vue Js / Scss / HTML

PHP / Nodejs / C#

MySQL/SQLServer/Redis

Docker

Apache / Nginx / Centos

AWS

Gitlab / SVN

Experience

Docebo s.p.a / Software Engineer

February 2020 - Today, Biassono (MB)/Remote

Software developer in core product teams(LMS).

The main duties are maintenance and development of new features in our product area.

The main technologies used are: Angular, PHP, Mysql, Redis, docker, aws, gitlab.

The LMS is based on microservice architecture

Engitel s.p.a. / Software developer

November 2018 - January 2020, Milan

Software developer in the refactoring team for the main product (Spin&Go).

The main duties were the development with a new technologies to refactoring the CMS Spin&Go developed in ASP and scouting of new technologies.

The main technologies used were: VueJs, C#(.net core), SQLServer, svn. Sometimes I implemented custom SPA with Angular and vueJs.

Openworks s.r.l. / Software developer - System Administrator

November 2014 - October 2018, Milan

Software developer in the unique company development team. The main duties were maintenance and development of new features for the property LMS platform and moodle platforms. The main technologies used were: Javascript, PHP(propel), MySql. System administrator for the servers based on nginx and apache, the duties were: manage virtualhost and DNS, SSL installation and managed, FTP and SFTP users configuration, backup system implementation

Education

Bicocca University / Single course

2018, Milan

Single course of database 24/30

ITET Maggiolini / Diploma

September 2008 - June 2013, Parabiago(MI)

Diploma in computer science and accounting. Vote 77/100

Language

Italian - Native language

English - B1

Certification:

https://www.fluentify.com/cert/gabriele.m.32/1582630525-16861498 27-0b-0

Hobby

In my free time I love playing football with my friends, running and cycling.

Sometimes I try to study new skills with Udemy courses and I read some programming groups to will know a new technologies and approach.

I hereby authorize the use of my personal data in accordance to the GDPR 679/16 - "European regulation on the protection of personal data".